{
    "subject": "resource/454th_Bombardment_Group",
    "predicate": "property/awardName",
    "object": "Distinguished Unit Citation",
    "human_readable": "The 454th Bombardment Group was awarded a Distinguished Unit Citation.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9878647923469543,
            "question": "For what actions was the 454th Bombardment Group awarded a Distinguished Unit Citation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9321715235710144,
            "question": "What award was given to the 454th Bombardment Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9195490479469299,
            "question": "During what conflict might the 454th Bombardment Group have received this citation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8147189617156982,
            "question": "What type of military unit was the 454th Bombardment Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6368219256401062,
            "question": "How is a Distinguished Unit Citation typically presented?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6273174285888672,
            "question": "What does a Distinguished Unit Citation recognize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6212178468704224,
            "question": "What is the significance of receiving a Distinguished Unit Citation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6066417098045349,
            "question": "Can you name other military units that have received a Distinguished Unit Citation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4840463101863861,
            "question": "What impact might receiving a Distinguished Unit Citation have on the morale of a unit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46272891759872437,
            "question": "Are there any specific criteria that must be met to receive a Distinguished Unit Citation?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The 454th Bombardment Group was awarded a Distinguished Unit Citation.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1024_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact might receiving a Distinguished Unit Citation have on the morale of a unit?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1024_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other military units that have received a Distinguished Unit Citation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1024_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of receiving a Distinguished Unit Citation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1024_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1024_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1024_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1024_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1024_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1024_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1024_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1024_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1024_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1024_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1024_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to multiple files (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1024/re-ranker-msmarco/54.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1024/re-ranker-msmarco/36.txt), the 454th Bombardment Group was awarded a Distinguished Unit Citation for various missions, including an attack on an airfield at Bad V\u00f6slau, Austria on 12 April 1944 and an attack on steel factories at Linz, Austria."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that the 454th Bombardment Group earned two Distinguished Unit Citations during World War II, supporting the statement that it was awarded at least one Distinguished Unit Citation."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}